flixel.com 2014-02-10

# Flixel | Privacy

## Flixel Privacy Policy

This website and iPhone App is owned and operated by Flixel Photos Inc. (" **Flixel** "), of Canada. At Flixel, we recognize that people are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. Our Privacy Policy is based on _Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents_ Act, and _The Canadian Standards Association's Model Code for the Protection of Personal Information_. It also reflects our own belief about what is the right thing to do. We may update this Policy from time to time, so please check back if you are a regular visitor. Because of the nature of our website it is important that you read and understand the operation and use of our privacy policy and how it affects you.

Your use and access to this site is subject to the following terms and conditions and all applicable laws. By viewing or using this site, you agree to be bound by these terms, conditions, and laws. If you do not agree with any provision in this Privacy Policy and these Terms of Use, please do not use this site.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators and iPhone App Flixel collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Flixel’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Flixel’s visitors use its website and iPhone App. From time to time, Flixel may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website and iPhone App.

Flixel also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Flixel posts. Flixel only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Flixel’s website and iPhone App to voluntarily interact with Flixel in ways that require Flixel to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Flixel gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account on http://flixel.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, Flixel collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Flixel. Flixel does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Flixel may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its website and iPhone App. Flixel may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Flixel does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Flixel discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Flixel’s behalf or to provide services available at Flixel’s website and iPhone App, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Flixel’s website and iPhone App you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Flixel will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Flixel discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Flixel believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Flixel, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Flixel website and have supplied your email address, Flixel may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Flixel and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Flixel takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Flixel uses cookies to help Flixel identify and track visitors, their usage of the Flixel website and iPhone App and their website and iPhone App preferences. Flixel visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Flixel’s website, with the drawback that certain features of Flixel’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites and iPhone App be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Flixel and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Flixel Cinemagraph Pro Features**

Paid pro features are subject to change anytime without prior notice. Flixel will do its best to supplement any existing features bought with more improved features updated that are of similar effect at no extra charge. Due to Flixel’s commitment in providing the fastest and best visual experience possible, we reserve the right to modify any Pro features in the future. In essence, a paid feature is owned for as long as the feature is available in the App and we reserve the right to eliminate or modify them anytime. 

**HD Flixels**

**Paid HD capabilities are subject to change anytime without prior notice. It is always recommended that HD Flixels are saved in the camera roll to ensure access at all times.**

**Unsolicited Ideas**

Flixel cannot protect your unsolicited ideas, suggestions or materials related to our products, and we reserve the right to share non-personal information received via this site with the public. We do not seek unsolicited ideas, suggestions or materials related to our products. If you do not want Flixel to use your ideas to improve our products, please do not submit them to us.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Flixel may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Flixel’s sole discretion. Flixel encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site and iPhone App after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Personal Information of Minor Children**

**_Important Note to Parents_ :** Flixel does not include information or content on this site that is intentionally directed at minor children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from kids on our site. All of our contests require that participants be adults. __**_Important Note to Children_ :** Before providing your name, address, email address, or any other personal information to anyone on the Internet, be sure to ask your parents if it is okay
